let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "In the C language, the constant is defined _______.",
    answer: "Anywhere, but starting on a new line.",
    options: [
      "Before main",
      "After main",
      "Anywhere, but starting on a new line.",
      "None of the these."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the 16-bit compiler allowable range for integer constants?",
    answer: "-32768 to 32767",
    options: [
      "-3.4e38 to 3.4e38",
      "-32767 to 32768",
      "-32668 to 32667",
      "-32768 to 32767"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Each instance of a class has a different set of",
    answer: "Attribute values",
    options: [
      "Class interfaces",
      "Methods",
      "Return types",
      "Attribute values"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which is valid expression in c language?",
    answer: "int my_num = 100000;",
    options: [
      "int my_num = 100,000;",
      "int my_num = 100000;",
      "int my num = 1000;",
      "int my num == 10000;"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "If addition had higher precedence than multiplication, then the value of the expression (1 + 2 * 3 + 4 * 5) would be which of the following?",
    answer: "105",
    options: [
      "27",
      "47",
      "69",
      "105"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What does this statement mean? (x - = y + 1; ) ",
    answer: "x = x - y - 1",
    options: [
      "x = x - y + 1",
      "x = -x - y - 1",
      "x = x + y - 1",
      "x = x - y - 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: " Array is a _________ data structure.",
    answer: "Linear",
    options: [
      "Non-linear",
      "Primary",
      "Linear",
      "Data type"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "A global variable is declared __________.",
    answer: "Outside of the function",
    options: [
      "With the function",
      "Anywhere in the program",
      "Outside of the function",
      "Inside of the function"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: " Which of the following function is used to write the integer in a file?",
    answer: "putw()",
    options: [
      "getw()",
      "putw()",
      "int value",
      "f_int()"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following keywords is used to prevent any kind of change in a variable?",
    answer: "const",
    options: [
      "continue",
      "const",
      "struct",
      "extern"
    ]
  },
];